Guide to the Records of the Institute of African American Affairs RG.9.8
New York University Archives
- Series III: Earl S. Davis Correspondence, 60498
  - Black Films, 1975; 60919 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Blacks in Higher Education Articles, 1975; 60918 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Black Student Service Center, 1975; 60917 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, Dr. Roscoe Brown, 1975; 60916 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - IAAA Advisory, 1975; 60915 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1975; 60914 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - IAAA Graduate Planning Center Student Information Sheet, 1975; 60913 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - IAAA Graduate Planning Center Student Information Sheet, 1975; 60912 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - IAAA Graduate Planning Center Student Information Sheet, 1975; 60911 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - IAAA Graduate Planning Center Student Information Sheet, 1975; 60910 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - IAAA Informal Seminar Series, 1975; 60909 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - IAAA Mainstream (WNYU Radio Show), 1975; 60908 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - IAAA Planning, 1975; 60907 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - The Institute of the Black World Monthly Report, 1975; 60906 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Journalism Council, Inc., 1975; 60905 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1975; 60904 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1975; 60903 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1975; 60902 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1975; 60901 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1975; 60900 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Reception, 1975; 60899 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Scholarships/Correspondence, 1975; 60898 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Program-Memorial, 1975; 60897 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - NYU Report Biweekly/Journal, 1975; 60896 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Proposal Writing Workshop, 1975; 60895 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Still Here Magazine, 1975; 60894 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence - W. Barbee, 1975; 60893 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1975; 60892 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Art Collection-Grey Art Gallery, 1975; 60891 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Association of Black Faculty, 1975; 60890 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Bicentennial Celebration (IAAA at NYU), 1976; 60889 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Black Films, William Greaves, 1976; 60888 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Black Genealogy Book Compilation, 1976; 60887 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1977; 60839 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226040 9
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1977; 60838 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series, 1976; 60886 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: (2) Baraka, Amiri, 1976; 60885 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: (3) Booth, Judge W., 1976; 60884 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: (4) Coombs, Ode., 1976; 60883 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: (5) Higgins, Jr., Chester, 1976; 60882 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: (6) Tolliver, Melba, 1976; 60881 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - IAAA Seminars and Lectures: Attendees, 1976; 187229 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Boys Club of America in conjunction with IAAA, 1976; 60880 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Black Student Service Center, 1976; 60879 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Ebony Patriots Magazine, 1976; 60878 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - IAAA Graduate Planning Center Student Information Sheet, 1976; 60877 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - IAAA Graduate Planning Center Student Information Sheet, 1976; 60876 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - IAAA Informal Seminar Series, 1976; 60875 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - IAAA Inventory, 1976; 60874 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - IAAA Program Planning, 1976; 60873 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - IAAA Summary of the Activities of the Institute of Afro-American Affairs, 1976; 60869 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - IAAA Project - Ethnic Heritage Studies Program: The Role of Black Women in American Society, 1976; 60872 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - IAAA Seminar - 20th Century Black Radicalism, 1976; 60871 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - IAAA Staff Correspondence, 1976; 60870 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Institutional Racism: Implications for Social Workers, 1976; 60868 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Journalism Articles/Guide-Directory, 1976; 60867 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther - Graduate Certificates, 1976; 60866 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther - Graduate Certificates, 1976; 60865 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther - Graduate Certificates, 1976; 60864 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther - Graduate Certificates, 1976; 60863 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther - Graduate Reception, 1976; 60862 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther - Memorial, 1976; 60861 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Leadbelly Screening and Chronology, 1976; 60860 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - The Little Black Book, 1976; 60859 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - New York University Report Newspaper, 1976; 60858 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Secretarial Recruitment, 1976; 60856 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Sports Foundation, Inc., 1976; 60855 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Still Here Magazine, 1976; 60854 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Survey of Undergraduate Black Studies Courses at NYU, 1976; 60853 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1977; 60852 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Association of Black Faculty, 1977; 60851 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series, 1976-1977; 60850 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series, 1977; 187266 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Gil Noble, 1977; 60849 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: John O. Killens, 1977; 60848 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Basil Peterson, 1977; 60847 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Franklin Williams, 1977; 60846 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Mary Lou Williams, 1977; 60845 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Black Student Service Center, 1977; 60844 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Black Studies Research: Articles from 1969-1970, 1977; 60843 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Black Studies Research: Articles from 1973-1977, 60842 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1977; 60841 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1977; 60840 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - IAAA Annual Report-Proposed Plans/Programs, 1977; 60837 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - IAAA For Your Information, 1977; 60836 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1977; 60835 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduation Reception, 1977; 60834 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduation Reception, Student Responses, 1977; 60833 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Memorial, 1977; 60832 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226041 7
  - Literary Associations, 1977; 60831 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - National Conference of Artists, 1977; 60830 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - National Conference of Artists, 1977; 60829 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - New York University Report Newspaper, 1977; 60828 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - The New York Urban Coalition, 1977; 60827 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Police Athletic League, 1977; 60826 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Schomberg, Arthur A. Award Dinner at the Waldorf Astoria, 1977; 60825 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Sports Foundation, Inc., 1977; 60824 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Woodruff, Hale, 1977; 60823 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Black Creation Magazine, 1977; 60822 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - IAAA Graduate Planning Center Student Information Sheet, 1977; 60821 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - IAAA Newsletter, 1977; 60820 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - IAAA Newsletter, 1977; 60819 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1978; 60818 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Afro-American Cultural Foundation, 1978; 60817 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Association of Black Faculty, 1978; 60816 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Black Collegian Magazine, 1978; 60815 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series, 1978; 60814 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Lenox Hinds, 1978; 60813 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Benjamin Hooks, 1978; 60812 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Dr. Inez Smith Reid, 1978; 60811 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Ntozake Shange, 1978; 60810 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: John A. Williams, 1978; 60809 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Blacks in Higher Education Articles, 1978; 60808 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Cinque Gallery Board Meetings, 1978; 60807 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, W. Barbee, 1978; 60806 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Graduate Student Reception, 1978; 60805 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1978; 60804 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1978; 60803 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - IAAA For Your Information, 1978; 60802 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - IAAA Graduate Planning Center, Forms/Responses, 1978; 60801 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - IAAA Inventory, 1978; 60800 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - IAAA Newsbrief, 1978; 60799 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - IAAA Program Assistant, 1978; 60798 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - IAAA Space Inventory, 1978; 60797 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - IAAA Staff Projects/Activities, 1978; 60796 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - The Little Black Book Magazine, 1978; 60795 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Bibliographical Outline, 1978; 60794 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Bibliographical Outline, 1978; 60793 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Association (First Annual Awards Dinner), 1978; 60792 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1978; 60791 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduation Reception, 1978; 60790 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Memorial, 1978; 60789 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Scholarship Fund, 1978; 60788 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - New York University Report Publication, 1978; 60787 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - The New York Urban Coalition, 1978; 60786 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Second International Congress on Education, 1978; 60785 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence- Dr. Edward M. Carroll, 1978; 60784 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - ABFA Minority Student Achievement Award Recipients, 1979; 60783 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226042 5
  - ABFA Minority Student Achievement Award Recipients, Correspondence, 1979; 60782 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1979; 60781 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Afro-American Studies Program, 1979; 60780 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Black History Month Planning, 1979; 60779 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Black History Month Planning, 1979; 60778 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Black Literature, 1979; 60777 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Black Religion, news articles, 1979; 60776 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Correspondence and General Information, 1979; 60775 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: Dr. John Henrik Clarke, 1979; 60774 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: Dr. Edyth J. Gaines, 1979; 60773 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: Dr. Jeanne Noble, 1979; 60772 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: Gordon Parks, 1979; 60771 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: James Steele, 1979; 60770 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Black Studies Programs in the U.S., 1979; 60769 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Black Student Service Center, 1979; 60768 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Cinque Gallery Board Meetings, 1979; 60767 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Dr. Edward M. Carroll, Acting Director, IAAA, 1979; 60766 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Earl Davis, Director-IAAA, 1979; 60765 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Fundraising, IAAA, 1979; 60764 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Graduate Student Reception, 1979; 60763 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1979; 60762 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1979; 60761 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - IAAA Black Student Organization Steering Committee Meeting, 1979; 60760 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - IAAA Brochure, 1979; 60759 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - IAAA Program Planning, 1979; 60758 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - IAAA Questionnaire - Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Material Packet, 1979; 60757 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Reception, 1979; 60756 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther, Memorial Ceremony, 1979; 60755 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther, Memorial Ceremony, 1979; 60754 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther, Memorial Ceremony, 1979; 60753 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Monograph Series, Volume I, Number I, 1979, 60752 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Renwick Reception, 1979; 60751 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Research-Enrollment/Black Studies Courses Offered at NYU, 1979; 60750 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Secretarial Recruitment, 1979; 60749 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Washington Square News, 1979; 60748 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - ABFA Constitution, 1980; 60747 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Afro-American Courses and Related Subjects Listing, 1980; 60746 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Benin Exhibition Correspondence, 1980; 60745 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series General Correspondence, 1980; 60744 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Black Scholars Series Speakers: "Economic Development in the Black Community: 'What Will the 80's Bring?'" by Arthur H. Barnes, 1980; 60743 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Black Scholars Series Speakers: "The Black Image in the Media" by David Lampel, 1980; 60742 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Black Scholars Series Speakers: "Metamorphosis-Poetry Reading" Featuring Quincy Troupe, Fred Nelson, Regina Williams, Mariah Britton Howard, Wayne Providence, Cathering Sanders, 1980; 60741 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Black Scholars Series Speakers: "The 80's - Which Way for Black America," Guest Speaker Congressman Charles B. Rangel, 1980; 60740 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - BSSC, 1980; 60739 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - BSSO, 1980; 60738 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Black Studies Programs Research, 1980; 60737 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Citicorp/NYU Business Career Forum for Minority Undergraduate Students, 1980; 60736 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Citicorp/NYU Business Career Forum for Minority Undergraduate Students, 1980; 60735 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Citicorp/NYU Business Career Forum for Minority Undergraduate Students, 1980; 60734 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence - Earl Davis, Director, 1980; 60733 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226043 3
  - Correspondence - Louise Dennis, 1980; 60732 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "Emerging African Nations," Correspondence - Ambassadors, Conference, 1980; 60731 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - "Emerging African Nations," Forms, 1980; 60730 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "Emerging African Nations," List of African Ambassadors, 1980; 60729 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - "Emerging African Nations," Program Operations, 1980; 60728 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising, 1980; 60727 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1980; 60726 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - IAAA Inventory, 1980; 60725 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - IAAA Lecturer/Speakers, 1980; 60724 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - IAAA Minority Advisory Council, 1980; 60723 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - IAAA Staff Meetings, 1980; 60722 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Jazz Seminars, 1980; 60721 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Association, 1980; 60720 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Memorial Ceremony, 1980; 60719 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Memorial Ceremony, 1980; 60718 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Memorial Ceremony, 1980; 60717 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Citicorp/NYU Business Career Forum - Forms, 1980; 60716 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Citicorp/NYU Business Career Forum - Correspondence, 1980; 60715 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - IAAA For Your Information, 1980; 60714 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Leadership Workshop - Minority Advisory Council (MAC), 1980; 60713 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Minority Student Award, 1980; 60712 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Minority Student Recruitment at NYU, 1980; 60711 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - The NY Urban Coalition, 1980; 60710 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Organization of Black Women (OBW), 1980; 60709 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Orientation, NYU, 1980; 60708 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Secretarial Recruitment, 1980; 60707 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - A Social Worker's Critique of the Afro-American Experience by Mary Hall, 1980; 60706 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Survey of Black Studies Courses Offered throughout the University From 1970-1979 and Summary, 1980; 60705 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Survey of Black Studies Courses Offered throughout the University From 1970-1979 and Summary, 1980; 60704 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Survey of Black Studies Courses Offered throughout the University From 1970-1979 and Summary, 1980; 60703 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Survey of Black Studies Courses Offered throughout the University From 1970-1979 and Summary, 1980; 60702 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Survey of Black Studies Courses Offered throughout the University From 1970-1979 and Summary, 1980; 60701 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Survey of Black Studies Courses Offered throughout the University From 1970-1979 and Summary, 1980; 60700 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - ABFA Correspondence, 1981; 60699 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - ABFA Minutes of Meetings, 1981; 60698 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1981; 60697 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Correspondence, 1981; 60696 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Questionnaire, 1981; 60695 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Thomas S. Jacobs, "Criminal Justice System", 1981; 60694 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series Speakers: Michelle Wallace, "Black Macho and the Myth of the Superwoman", 1981; 60693 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Black Student Organizations at NYU, 1981; 60692 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Black Student Service Center, 1981; 60691 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Citicorp/NYU Business Career Forum for Minority Undergraduate Students, 1981; 60690 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence - E. Davis, 1981; 60689 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Fundraising, 1981; 60688 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Girls Town, 1981; 60687 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1981; 60686 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - IAAA Advisory Board, 1981; 60685 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - IAAA Advisory Council, 1981; 60684 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1981; 60683 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - IAAA Black Choir, 1981; 60682 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - IAAA For Your Information, 1981; 60681 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - IAAA Minority Advisory Council, 1981; 60680 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - IAAA Office Move, 1981; 60679 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226044 1
  - IAAA Office Move, 1981; 60678 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Minority Student Association Correspondence, 1981; 60677 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Monograph Series, 1981; 60676 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - UNESCO, 1981; 60675 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Williams, Sylvia "KUUMBA": Blacks in Theatre, 1981; 60674 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Benin Exhibition Catalog Publicity, 1982; 60673 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - "Black Theatre Forum: A Total Perspective" Questionnaires RESTRICTED, 1982; 60672 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Catholic Interracial Council of NY, 1982; 60671 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, E. Davis, 1982; 60670 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Funding Resources, 1982; 60669 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1982; 60668 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1982; 60667 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1982; 60666 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1982; 60665 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - IAAA Brochure, 1982; 60664 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - IAAA Library Books Receipts, 1982; 60663 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - The International Law Review of Developing Nations (ILRDN) Journal Proposal, 1982; 60662 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - National Urban League, Inc. Disease Prevention/Health Promotion in Urban Black Communities Project Advisory Committee, 1982; 60661 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases of IAAA Events, 1982; 60660 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Reservations, IAAA, 1982; 60659 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - UNESCO, 1982; 60658 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Black Student Organizations at NYU, 1982; 60657 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - African American Book Resources and Listing, 1980-1983; 60656 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Black Politics: Compilation of Articles Ranging from 1972-1983, 60655 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Black Social Workers Research, 1983; 60654 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Black Student Organizations, 1983; 60653 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Black Student Organizations, 1983; 60652 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Black Studies and Related Courses, 1983; 60651 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Burrows, Vinnie - Profile, 1983; 60650 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Community Groups / organizations, 1983; 60649 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, Earl Davis, 1983; 60648 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Film, Television and Art, 1983; 60647 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226045 8
  - Film, Television and Art, 1983; 60646 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Funding Resources, 1983; 60645 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - HEOP Higher Education Opportunities Program Background Information, 1983; 60644 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1983; 60643 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - News Articles Sports Related, 1983; 60642 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - NYU Photos, 1983; 60641 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Petty Cash Vouchers and Receipts, 1983; 60640 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Purchasing, 1983; 60639 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Research on Afro-American Adult Development "Journey Through Transitions" Questionnaire, 1983; 60638 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Transfiguration Lutheran Church, 1983; 60637 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Transfiguration Lutheran Church, 1983; 60636 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - UNESCO, 1983; 60635 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - UNESCO, 1983; 60634 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - American Committee on Africa, 1984; 60633 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Black Lifestyles Course/School of Social Work, 1984; 60632 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Brown Plus Thirty Conference Sponsored by Metro Center, 1984; 60631 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Citicorp/NYU Business Career Forum for Minority Undergraduate Students, 1984; 60630 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Community Groups / Organizations, 1984; 60629 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Congressional Black Caucus, 1984; 60628 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence - Trisha Brown, 1984; 60627 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - Barbara Burce, 1984; 60626 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence - Earl S. Davis, 1984; 60625 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Course Listing, Black Studies and Related Courses, 1984; 60624 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - HEOP Higher Education Opportunities Program, 1984; 60623 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - IAAA Event Newspaper Ads, 1984; 60622 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1984; 60621 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1984; 60620 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - IBM Recruitment, 1984; 60619 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Jackson, Jesse, 1983-1984; 60618 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Morrison, Toni, 1984; 60617 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - NYU Black Student Organizations Correspondence, 1984; 60616 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - NYU Black Student Organizations Publicity, 1984; 60615 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Petty Cash Vouchers and Receipts, 1984; 60614 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Petty Cash Vouchers and Receipts, 1984; 60613 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Piper, Ralph, NYU Student - Term Paper, 1984; 60612 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - UNESCO, 1984; 60611 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Gerald Spence, 1984; 60610 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226046 6
  - AEJ Correspondence, 1985; 60609 (Box 29, Folder 3)